Profile

Very strong organizational skills, ability to pick up new processes and procedures quickly, extremely social, highly motivated, team worker, and dedicated to completing the task at hand. I have worked a multitude of jobs, all in which requires me to have excellent customer service personality.

Skills

- Resourceful problem solver
- Fast Pace worker
- Quick Learner
- Efficient in Microsoft Programs:
 - Word
 - Power Point
 - Excel
- Organizational Skills:
 - Scheduling
 - Time Management
 - Assertive
 - Hands On worker

Experience

STUDENT, UCLA EXTENSION WESTWOOD, CA MAY 2021

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- GitHub

RECEPTION, (FELKER, TOCKZEK, SUDDLESON, ABRAMSON, LLP) LOS ANGELES, CA JUNE 2018-2021

- Received all incoming calls and directed to needed personal.
- Extensive work in Outlook, iManagement, and iEntertainment.
- Worked on Excel to log incoming checks and W2 statements.
- Assistant to Office Manager, Accountant, and Administrator.
- Created Invoices for clients.
- Data Management for new and existing clients in iEntertainment.
- Manage postal service for income and outgoing mail.
- Troubleshooting technical problems in office.
 - Computer problems
 - Printer problems
 - Phone issues
 - Server Mangement

BARTENDER, BENIHANA'S, SANTA MONICA, CA JUNE 2016-2019

- Able to craft a variety of cocktails, shooters, and mixed drinks.
- Do to the nature of the position I am excellent at serving lunch and dinner courses. Also, bussing my bar and tables surrounding it.
- Restocking and prepping for future incoming customers.
- Taking and recording inventory.
- Able to pour and serve draft beers correctly.

DISK JOCKEY (DJ) LIVE ENGINEER, YNOT ENERTAINMENT, LOS ANGELES, CA - MAY 2008-2020

- Lapprenticed with two DJ's.
- Calculating the demographics of a facility to set up DJ equipment, i.e., speakers, bass cabinets, lights, mixer, turntables, to achieve the best auditory harmonics.
- Master of Ceremonies; catering ceremonies to fit the demographic of the crowd.
- Playing music to fit the setting in mood of the occasion.
- Inventory control of equipment.

• Purchasing goods and equipment.

FOOD CARRIER, GRUBHUB, SANTA MONICA, CA – FEBRUARY 2015- APRIL 2016
DECISION MAKING IN ORDER TO ASSURE PROPER TIME MANAGEMENT FOR THE TIMELY PICKING UP AND DE-LIVERY OF FOOD.

- Regular and ongoing communication between employer and customers.
- Solving delivery problems due to restaurant delays, traffic, etc.
- Building professional and collaborative relationships with the restaurants and customers as representing the face of GrubHub and myself.

DRIVER, LYFT, SANTA MONICA, CA-MAY 2014- FEBRUARY 2015

- Built versatile customer interactions to establish inviting atmospheres.
- Set my own schedule/timetable.
- Chose work locations based on demand.
- Helped customers with packages/luggage.

ASSISTANT A&R, SONY RECORDS, BURBANK, CA - JUNE 2013- MAY 2014

- Internship which involved:.
 - Screened issues before they met the manager. Planned and reviewed the schedule for each day.
 - Constant note taking and reminder settings in a very interactive environment.
 - Personal driver to all events of the day.
 - Created charts and background information regarding our artist in scope.
 - Drafted and responded to artist, producers, and other crucial cliental.
 - Filtered instrumentals and lyrics before reaching further in the process.

CREW MEMBER, MCDONALDS, LOS ANGELES, CA - JUNE 2011-DECEMBER 2012

- Frequently rotated in the following work stations/job duties:
 - Front counter,
 - Drive through window,
 - Kitchen worker/cook.
- Helped drive sales goals and achieve monthly standard for the mystery shopper.



- Resolved customer complaints and conflicts.
- Restocking and documenting all product.
- I worked on a very flexible schedule and was able to take all shifts from opening, closing, weekend, and holidays.

Education

UCLA Extension, Westwood, California - Full Stack bootcamp May, 2021

Santa Monica College, Santa Monica, California – Associates in Computer Science May, 2018 to Present

Santa Monica College, Santa Monica, California – Music Major, Business Minor May, 2013 to 2016

Santa Monica College, Santa Monica, California – Art Major, Music Minor May, 2010 to 2013